Yerin An. Jarvis Consulting

I am a junior software developer with Jarvis and graduate from Centennial College with an Advanced Diploma of Software Engineering Technology. Also, I have a bachelor's degree in Architecture. I have always been passionate about new technology and thinking of integrating technology into our daily lives. And it gives me to motivate and learn that can improve myself. I have experience as a back-end developer for around a year, and I worked with REST APIs, data analytics, and application development. I look forward to working in data engineering and getting a chance to contribute to the innovations.

Skills

Proficient: Java, Linux/Bash, RDBMS/SQL, Agile/Scrum, Git, REST APIs, SpringBoot, Hibernate

Competent: JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Python, Docker, Algorithms/Data structures, Jupyter notebook, Pandas

Familiar: C#, Vue, Android, React, Angular

Jarvis Projects

Project source code: https://github.com/jarviscanada/jarvis data eng YerinAn

Cluster Monitor [GitHub]: Developed an internal tool to collect and save both server hardware specifications and ongoing Linux resource usage data so that users can know their cluster status better. Utilized the docker container to provision the database—Created bash scripts for monitoring nodes—Developed SQL queries to store and retrieve data

Core Java Apps [GitHub]:

• Twitter App: In development

- JDBC App: Implemented an application that uses JDBC to build a connection between Java and PostgreSQL database. developed CRUD operations by using the DAO design pattern.
- Grep App: Developed an application that has the functionality to a simplified the Linux grep command using Java. Used the lambda function and stream API from Java to optimize the final project performance.

Springboot App [GitHub]: In development

Python Data Analytics [GitHub]: In development

Hadoop [GitHub]: In development Spark [GitHub]: In development

Cloud/DevOps [GitHub]: In development

Highlighted Projects

MODERN ERP application [GitHub]: Created an application that any company or customer can make their online website based on their products and analyze the online business. Worked with Java 11, Vue, Javascript, Spring boot, and MS SQL.

WebGaming - Space defenders [GitHub]: Designed a web application which is a space shooting game that uses Typescript, Javascript and CreateJs, and it works with a keyboard. Adjusted three stages that the difficulty level through different enemies, options, items and a high scoreboard.

Professional Experiences

Software Developer, Jarvis (2021-present): Developed Data Engineering projects in Java using technologies such as Git, Java, Maven, Docker, Springboot, RDBMS/SQL, Python. Collaborated with a team in daily Scrum meetings to implement Agile development practices.

Backend Developer, Centennial College (2020-2021): migrated a legacy medical application from Flex code to Java 11 using Spring Framework and Angular. Created Spring Rest APIs to persist, merge, delete and list patients, encounters, billings, etc. Replaced some Hibernate/JPQL queries with MSSQL/SQL native queries to increase some routers' performance. Created and merge branches to manage the code version using Github Supported the frontend teams with bug triage, troubleshooting/debugging and resolution (Jira for tickets and Confluence for API documentation)

Created test stubs for unit testing, system testing and integration testing using JUnit Participated in resolving technical issues that arise during development Participated in Agile Scrum meetings. Excellent written and verbal communication skills with my supervisors and co-workers

UX/UI designer & Web developer | Co-op, AlterSpark-Digital Psychology & Behaviour Design (2019): Worked as a web developer and assisted our team in migrating a psychological website from bootstrap3 to bootstrap4. Also, I developed a dashboard with charts using Javascript and showing analyzed personal based on the pictures and profiles with some machine learning models. Built heatmaps, charts using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and NodeJS Built photoprograms that can resize, reduce resolution, and rename with Python and Django Analyzed pictures using classification Develop web sites using bootstrap4 Built photo library with JSON

Education

Centennial College (2017-2020), Advanced Diploma of Software Engineering Technology, Electrical and Computer Engineering

Hoseo University (2005-2011), Bachelor Degree of Architecture, Architecture

Miscellaneous

- Psychology for Digital Behavior Change [DBC1] (2019)
- Psychological Architectures of Digital Behavior Change [DBC2] (2019)
- Certificate of Completion for the workshop Emotional Design Psychology [EDP] (2019)
- Music composing, DJing, guitar
- Competitive gaming
- Collecting Lego